{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_Hutton",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Newcastle-on-Tyne",
    "human_readable": "Charles Hutton was born in Newcastle-on-Tyne.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8768236041069031,
            "question": "Where was Charles Hutton born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8635768890380859,
            "question": "Name the city where Charles Hutton was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7761640548706055,
            "question": "In what century was Charles Hutton born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5515194535255432,
            "question": "What is Charles Hutton known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4704835116863251,
            "question": "Was Charles Hutton a mathematician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41169583797454834,
            "question": "What field is Charles Hutton associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4017375707626343,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Charles Hutton's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40053674578666687,
            "question": "During what period did Charles Hutton live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36531707644462585,
            "question": "What are some of Charles Hutton's notable works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17710798978805542,
            "question": "What impact did Charles Hutton have on mathematics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles Hutton was born in Newcastle-on-Tyne.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2994_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Charles Hutton's notable works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2994_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During what period did Charles Hutton live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2994_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Charles Hutton's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2994_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2994_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}\n\nThe documents mention multiple times that Charles Hutton was born in Newcastle or Newcastle-upon-Tyne. This confirms that the statement \"Charles Hutton was born in Newcastle-on-Tyne\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently state that Charles Hutton was born in Newcastle, which is commonly referred to as Newcastle-on-Tyne."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}